you are welcome to another edition of
orange vibes i represent to you unfpa
garnish activities over the past week
for our headlines prudential life
insurance ghana partners unfp governor
to assist vulnerable women during the
pandemic
uh in ghana hosts the fourth edition of
the youth impact series
unfpa ghana calls on partners to amplify
issues on women and girls
and will discuss on the key highlights
in the 2020 swap report sun preference
to our first story prudential life
insurance ghana has donated a sum
of 35 000 to unfpa ghana
to support the agency's efforts to
ensure that female headquarters properly
known as kaya are supported with
necessary items
to protect them against copper 19 while
providing
income generation skills and sexually
productive health and rights information
and education receiving the donation on
behalf of the country office
deputy representative of unfpa ghana dr
agnes nibarua
expressed her appreciation to prudential
life insurance ghana for their
contribution to the work of unfpa
highlighting that it will indeed go a
long way to bring to fruition
the mandates of the organization moving
on
the un youth group in ghana under the
auspices of u.n habitat organized the
fourth youth impact series on the theme
leaving no one behind the role of young
people in slums or informal settlements
in the kubernetes response and recovery
speakers included pharaoh brahma of the
people dialogue on human settlements
solomon teter of the community
development committee and now your
quantity
of the ghana federation for the urban
poor and was moderated by cynthia prabh
the webinar explored ways to stimulate
conversation
among and concerning young people for
cover 19 response and recovery
away from that the country
representative of unfpa ghana mr knee
ojo lakme has called on government and
partners
to pay attention to issues affecting
women such as child marriage
female genital mutilation and some
preference and the need to eliminate
them
this statement was made during his
appearance with the executive director
of the national population council
dr leticia appiah on gtv's prime time
talk show
talking points hosted by dr jk enim
wright
it was aimed at promoting issues of the
2020 swap report and the world
population day
now still on issues that undermine
equality a youth leaders fellow here at
unfpa
ghana sunam amusu joins me to discuss
the issue of sound preference among
families
as highlighted in the 2020 states of
world population report
when boys are valued more highly than
girls
the pressure to have a son is intense
did you know
that about a quarter of all parents with
two girls
may result to gender biotech selection
to avoid the breath of a third girl
some preference has led to imbalances in
the number of men
and women distorting the sex racial
balance
of countries populations and denying
them an opportunity
to contribute to development say no to
some preference
a voice can girls come too certainly
let's keep the conversation going on
unfpa garnet social media platforms
facebook instagram twitter and youtube
and remember stay safe
you